by H.
Thank you for watching!
And now, we're back with Bananaman from Nogizaka Public Shikai, thank you very much for watching.
And here's Nogizaka-chan!
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Se-no-snack!
Great!
Let's see what you have in store for us today, Mr. Himuro.
Let's have the battle to determine the strongest snack in Nogizaka!
The best snack!
What is this snack?
It's a snack.
Remember Kuromi's strongest snack a while ago?
Yes, yes, yes...
This is the most powerful snack... and when we ate it, everyone said...
Well, they're good, but...
They were good, but...
Then I talked about Heart Chipotle...
I said, "Well, let's decide next time.
But if we do it today...
It's a deciding game.
What do you think?
This time, we'll divide the members' favorite snacks into 4 categories
And we'll decide the number one in each category.
Then, we'll have them catered for future recordings.
For the dressing room.
That's a good idea.
They'll sell well... if they win first place.
It's going to sell like hotcakes.
We'll get commercials.
A commercial.
I'm not saying "Wow." I'm saying "Wow.
You've done a lot of commercials.
I love sweets.
I'd like to enter each category.
I'll do it.
Mr. Himura actually eats snacks.
Mr. Himura specializes in rice crackers.
When we do the rice cracker category, you can enter too, Himura-san.
Okay, thank you.
Himura-san eats them like he's hiding.
Like he's not eating.
Just a little gap in the radio.
He eats it so that he doesn't make a sound.
If you make noise, your wife will know.
I'll melt it inside.
I'm counting on you.
And here comes the best snack of the day!
Are you excited?
Please let me be a member!
This is amazing!
It's like a dream.
A top idol would be so happy with this.
Then what was all that fancy fruit for?
A box of these?
Do they all have smiles like this?
Isn't it easy to get a smile out of an idol?
Now, there's a rumor that a snack bar in Setagaya has gone missing.
I heard there's no more of that Kimpei, now.
I'm so happy to have this.
If you have any left over, please take some home!
This is super exciting, isn't it?
Let's start with the salty category.
7 products were entered with handwritten cups!
Is this from Kansai?
I'll definitely buy some at the airport when I'm on location in Kansai!
It's delicious...and the picture is great!
That means it's already good.
They're going away over there. They're persimmons, right?
It's wasashi.
Uncle Pearl, it's delicious!
Do Kansai people really eat this?
They eat a lot of this.
Try some.
Who hasn't tried it before?
I didn't know there were so many.
It's noisy when this many people open it.
Isn't this a dream? One bag per person.
It's so good.
Dashi flavor. You've never had it before?
I've never had it before. It tastes like Japanese soup stock, like bonito soup stock.
It's so good!
I've never had it before, but I think I like this one better.
But they don't sell Carl's anymore.
They're only sold in western Japan now, right?
So if Carl's wins first place this time...
It's tough, isn't it? I have to go all the way to Kansai to get backstage every time.
That's a lot of work.
Persimmons... Is this all you eat?
I used to eat them, and when I moved to Tochigi, they didn't sell them.
They don't sell thin-skinned persimmons.
So I asked my grandma to send me cardboard boxes of curls.
On the other hand, you never had cheese or curry?
No, it's too strong.
It's too light.
I still don't like the fact that they don't sell curls anymore.
Carl's is like that.
I thought Carl's would always be around.
I thought he was the king.
And who else used to eat them a lot? For the first time.
It was just something I took for granted.I took it for granted that they were available.
When I heard it was a limited edition, I thought I should have had it.
Well, I should have had it now.
I'm going back, aren't I?
I should have eaten it!
I have to go on and on to introduce you all!
Healthy!
This is a very adult image, isn't it?
This is a taste of the earth.
Taste of Earth.
Who's this?
Why?
I guess when I went abroad, they didn't sell Japanese potato chips.
When you go on vacation?
Or when I go on a skating trip.
When I go skating and want to feel Japan, I buy these.
I see.
Let's try some.
It's so thin, it doesn't show any color.
Thin is thin.
The color is thinner than thin
I love raisins.
Who can say no to this?
It's a classic.
But it's so popular!
Fried potato
My daughter loves them too!
I don't know why kataage is so good.
It's so good, young girls adore it!
Who's this?
Who is this?
Yum!
Of all the snacks I've ever eaten, I like the texture and saltiness the best!
The more you bite into it, the more delicious it gets!
It's the first time I've eaten them.
It might be the first time!
Yum!
First time.
I love these so much I'm buying two cardboard boxes about this big.
That's amazing.
I don't usually eat snacks like that.
Maybe only fried potatoes.
I thought, "He's so skinny, why would he eat candy?
And he didn't buy that size, he bought the big size.
Is there such a thing?
Yamashita, what's wrong?
It's so small!
Where is it?
There it is, there it is!
Nice! It's like a field trip!
It's hard to do this...
I think I like it.
I love it... but the black pepper...
It tastes like...
Black pepper manganese.
Why do they have these big bags of manganese pepper?
But this one's huge, and everyone else has a bunch of little ones.
Oh, poor baby.
I wouldn't eat that seriously.
This is definitely good, though.
Yum!
Makes me want a Coke.
You're right.
This is so good.
Jaga Shio Butter
Fried chicken flavor or something...
I'll teach you how to eat it my way!
Who's this?
This is me!
I love it already!
The other one is more famous.
Yes, but this one is the real deal.
This one's my favorite.
I like to eat a whole piece.
While almost injuring the roof of my mouth
While almost injuring the corners of my mouth.
Try this one.
Here we go.
You don't have to put it in.
So you're going to hit it between the signs.
Yes, I love to go all out.
I love to go all out.
Oh my God!
Be careful
It's dangerous, but it's good.
It's so crispy
This is really crispy!
This is so good!
Delicious.
Otttt... ott... ott... ott... ott...
Otttttt... they have a version of this.
Eventually, this one.
You're right. Otttttttt is good.
You know what I'm talking about.
You know who this is.
Ottttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttt!
I've eaten ottttttttos since I was a little girl.I've been familiar with eating ottttos since I was a little girl.
I think that's why many people don't bother to buy them.
I like it so much that I would buy it if I found it.
I'll eat it soon too!
I'm so happy!
You can't get this crispy texture anywhere else.
I can't get enough of it, so I eat it endlessly.
I used to wonder what kind of animal it was.
I did, and I still do.
There's a rare character.
Like a clione.
I'm happy when I get a clione.
I remember now.
I'm happy when I get a Clione.
So that's how it is.
And...
Hotellong.
I'm the one who brought out the hotelong.
That's right.
I ate it when I was a kid, and then as an adult, I became obsessed with it.
I even drink this stuff.
I see.
I can eat it and eat it and eat it.
It's the texture. That's why it's a little different.
Who likes hotela longs?
Hotterongs.
Everybody likes hotel rolls.
I even had it ranked number one in a survey.
That's right.
I'm sorry, that one on my side sucked.
I eat this every day.
Seriously.
I'm so addicted to them that I feel like each one has a different texture.
Some are rough, some are smooth.
Some have air in them and some don't.
I get it.
Hotellong is good.
It's the last one.
Amijaga.
I don't know this one.
I like the space... this space makes it taste better.
500 times better.
I don't know.
I really, really, really want a Coke.
What?
You don't have any for the members?
Sorry, we're the only ones with Coke.
Here you go.
Is it good?
Kinax and Coke.
No, it'll fly away.
Kinak & Cola
Forever truly love, tomorrow, regret?
Oh my God, I can't believe this is 55.
This is the best.
Let's go, Ami Jagger.
It's so cute. It looks like a car tire.
Who's this?
Oh, good job.
That's good.
I need this space now.
It's so good!
This space makes it taste even better.
This is good.
Ami Jäger is so good!
I can't stop.
Four.
And now, from the salt section, we all vote for our favorite snacks to have in the dressing room
First place, vegetable salted butter.
That's great. I'm so happy.
I think it would probably be a cheaper operation, so...
Yes, it is.
Cheap.
You didn't give it away.
I met a guy.
What's changed?
You went to Amija crab?
It was a bit revolutionary.
It's true.
Everyone who's watching TV right now is dying to try it.
Let's get the cola ready.
Here you go.
It's so good!
It's delicious.
It's sweet.
Next is the sweet snack category!
The members highly recommend 7 products, en plein air!
Caramel corn.
This is a forever favorite.
I remember begging my mom to buy it for me when I was little.
That's amazing.
I got one when I was little too.
How many caramel corn do you have?
I'm gonna go out on a limb and say this is number one.
In the sweet category.
We can all sing the Caramel Corn song, right?
Japanese people.
I don't know.
Caramel Corncaramel corn
Is it possible that I'm in a commercial right now?
I'm doing a commercial.
Tohut
Caramel Corn
Oh, no, no, no!
Seriously, they can all sing?
Delicious.
I haven't had one of these in a while.
Who dropped this?
Oh, man.
I knew it.
I've had it since I was a kid.
It's the most familiar.
You've got a nice voice.
Do you eat peanuts?
I love peanuts.
Peanuts are more honest.
It's like, "Oh, this is what makes it good.
Caramel corn is strong.
Next.
Oh, my God.
Cobbler's chip.
The new addictive soybean flour!
What the heck is this?
I love this!
It's a Korean snack.
I love soybean flour.
I can't tell from the first bite.
But after about the 5th bite...
I can't tell much from the first bite.
It's so light!
It's like an aerial.
It sure is.
It's new.
It's delicious.
It's new, isn't it?
You must have just discovered it recently.
I learned about it when Korean food and sweets were booming.
I used to eat them on the plane when I was traveling.
I'm surprised you didn't try it first.
I wouldn't go there either.
I would never touch it.
There was some buzz about it, and I think it was delicious.
Next...
This is Korean, too?
What's this?
Honey.
This is Korean, too.
Real tasty powder.
Who's this?
Nice. You like sweets.
I do.
Eat it.
It smells so good.
What's that wonderful smell?
I've smelled this before.
Bill Snacks.
I was just saying about the bill snacks this time.
Yum!
This is good.
Shocking!
But it's more like a bill snack.
Inspired by bill snacks.
Like Jiro-inspired.
This is delicious.
How did you find this?
Where can I find these?
I don't know. Supermarkets in different countries.
Like Haldi's.
Like Haldi.
They have them in places like that.
This is so good!
It's so good!
This is so good.
Next.
Hanabatake Farm's wreath sugar!
Looks delicious!
Hanawa Sugar...
This is right on the edge of the snack line.
It smells so good!
Simico-rich guilt.
This is so bad!
The smell is so bad!
Even before I ate it.
I kept putting it in my nose.
Wow, that's a really nice snake smell.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, my God.
You guys can't do this.
I can do this.
Oh, my God, this is so good!
This is so good!
Yum!
What the hell did you bring this?
This is so good!You got a bad one here.
This is so good!
This is a little bit crazy.
I love it so much.
You made me think it's a little foul in the "KARINTOH" department.
I'm like, "Is this really a kaharintou?
It's a snack!
It's a snack.
It's amazing!
I often buy them at Tokyo Station.
I often buy them at Tokyo Station, and they're in the souvenir section.
You go here often.
That's Yamashita!
You've got some great stuff.
You've got some great stuff here.
Whoever made this is a genius.
This is good.
Yum!
What's this?
And the nuts.
I love nuts!
I don't even know what nuts are.
I don't know any nuts either.
Nuts are bought by guys like Mr. Himura.
Are these snacks?
Try some.
What's so good about this?
It's me.
I'm here.
You should eat it all at once.
What's this?
It's good.
What?
Isn't this good?
Oh my God, this is good!
It's delicious!
It's like a candy or a caramel hardened around it.
It's good.
It's like candy, but...
You're a grown-up.
I'm gonna have a Coke with that.
I'd probably...
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I think I'm going to die.
I've had this at my parents' house since I was a kid.
Why is this in my parents' house?
Nuts.
I think it's my mom's favorite.
Mom.
No, they're good.
Oh, my God, Mom.
Oh, my God. I'll get you some of these.
Fudzuki.
You know, these fu-fu sweets...
They're so good that once you pass by, you go back for more.
I don't know, but this generation...
It says "I'm home.
You know who this is?
It's got this pop-up.
Oh, my God.
It's, like, the youngest one I've ever seen.
No, I love it.
I love butterscotch, and I love brown sugar.
I want the brown sugar one.
That's right.
The first time I tasted it, I thought it was a revolution.
They're good, aren't they?
The edges are good.
The edges are delicious.
Yes, just as it begins.
I can tell you're home.
Brown sugar stuff is good, right?
Yeah, it's good
It's good.
No, we keep a lot of fu crackers in the house.
That's great!
They have a discount version, don't they?
Yes.
My mom used to buy them for me and I ate them all my life.
But this...
It's like a super cheap palm tree!
I can eat a long one in a day.
Sightseeing spots...
Yes, it's good.
Fu confectionery is good.
It's delicious.
I'll get to the best part.
Last but not least!
I love Umaibo wow!
Have you ever tried the sugar rusk flavor?
Have you? If you haven't, you're in for a shock.
You know what they say, "Don't underestimate Umaibo.
Try some of this.
Wait a minute. Did you just crush Yamashita?
Why don't I cut it into quarters?
It's so obvious.
I don't know how to crush a circle.
You just called it "beko"?
I've never seen him do that before.
Really?Seriously?
I'm trying to divide it into four equal parts.
It's not good.
No, but it's easier for a girl to eat that way.
Seriously?
It's delicious.
You don't like it either?
I won't touch it.
I only eat salami and cod roe.
Right, cheese?
It's good.
If you lick it...
Huh? Huh?
Like a...
Umaibo?
It's so good.
I can't believe it's a good stick.
You've never had one before?
No, never.
You know who's had them?
They're good.
They're delicious.
If you eat a lot of sweets.
I can't decide.
Wow!
It's just like the Koshien qualifiers in Kanagawa, isn't it?
So strong here!
So the winner of the strongest Amabumon is...
I can't decide.
Karinto 10 seconds
That was a shocker, that's for sure.
It was delicious!
This is going to sell!
This was on the nose.
I've never seen anything like it.
Now we're going to discover cheese!
The battle to determine the best snack, followed by the cheese flavor!
Now the aerial!
Let's start with the aerial.
This is good!
The four layers create a delicious container.
It's the container, right?
What? That's a great container for a candy bar.
How do you know?
I don't know what a good container is, but it's what you used to call it.
I've been regretting what I wrote for as long as I can remember.
It's okay.
Nice choice of container.
You've got it.
They're using it.
Yeah, but it's the texture, right?
No, it's called an aerial.
It's good, isn't it?
It's genius, if you think about it.
Why does Kawasaki roll them around in your mouth so much before you eat them?
I picked the darkest cheese one, and I was enjoying it.
He was nodding his head inside.
This is good, isn't it?
These are good!
This is hitting the high snacks section.
My adult lover.
I want you by my side forever.
Who's this?
There it is!
Why an adult lover?
I don't know. It's like a candy for adults.
It goes really well with alcohol.
I've loved them since I was little.
I thought it was genius.
It's just like that.
It's not a recreation, it's cheese.
It's cheese.
It's cheese... grilled cheese!
That's right!
Yum! It's so good!
Here you go!
I heard it tastes even better in a toaster oven.
Oh, really?
It's not just about the food!
Girl!
This is really delicious!
It's really good!
Delicious!
Here it is!
I like sweet ones, too.
I don't really eat cheese.
Shocking!
Shocking.
It's so soft and fluffy.
It melts.
I even love the way it gets stuck in my teeth.
Who could that be?
Oh, yes!
This is so good.
I love it.
Wow!
This is...
Wow.
I don't remember them being this soft.
Seriously, what is this?Seriously, what is it?
Ew.
No, I see.
There's nothing left.
These are so good!
I'm sure you've all had Jagariko cheese flavor before.
Let's see...
I don't have any.
The green one over there.
The green one.
This is good.
Just the right amount of cheese.
I can't find any giraffes.
That's me.
You don't have to say that.
The cheese-flavored one.
I liked the green one.
I ate too much green.
If I eat too much green...
I change to this one.
When I was in junior high.
We gathered in a park and ate nothing but green.
All of us.
I'm afraid of being a delinquent like that.
If you're a delinquent...
I have to eat it myself.
Why this punk?
It's him, isn't it?
He's cute.
The guy who does this is cute.
Do it in the park.
Park.
Hey, you're smoking eggs, right?
Jarariko.
Jararicos.
Good, good, good, good.
Stand on your head.
And here we go.
Wow, what is this?
This is Korean.
I don't know about you, but it's Korean.
Oh, my God, it's gone.
Oh, my God.
What's that? There it is!
You can draw like that?
I'm really good at pop art.
I used to work part-time at a convenience store.
Do they have pop-ups in convenience stores?
I couldn't do anything like that... but I couldn't read, order, or set up the shelves... so I spent 3 out of 5 hours drawing pop-ups.
I spent 3 hours out of 5 drawing pop-ups.
I couldn't do it!
Why can't you do it?
What is this? It's Korean, isn't it?
Yes, Korean.
I have a friend there.
What?
You have a friend in Korea?
I think of him as my friend.
He's Sate.
It's okay.
He sent it to me.
I can't believe he sent it to me if he's your friend.
How do you know him?
What flavor?
Cheese.
That was fast.
Oh, I was surprised. I've been eating the strong stuff for so long, I didn't taste it when I put it in.
That's for sure.
It came gradually. It came gradually.
Good, good, good, good.
It's good, and the texture is good, too.
It's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good.
It's good, it's good, it's good, it's good.
I'm addicted to it.
Yes, it is.
I know.
Last but not least, ladies and gentlemen.
Cheese bits.
Cheese bits are so good.
I used to love cheese bits.
This is my recommendation... but you guys know...
I know who you are.
Cheese bits are, well, they're good.
It's good.
Yeah, they're good.
It's got that crunchy texture.
Yeah, it's good.
It's a classic. It's a classic for our generation.
People don't know what's going on anymore.
It's good. It's good.
It's good.
So, what would you like to see in the cheese department backstage?
I did it!
Hey, Kaki, don't be such a loser!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
So, Cheeza is the winner!
Cheeza wins!
Wait a minute... these three are really strong here.
These three...
These three are so good at this kind of project!
There are more to come!There's more.
Strong.
Cheezazli.
That's cheese.
It's not cheating.
It's the cheesiest cheese.
Yes, it is.
No, it's fun.
It's fun.
And the people watching can buy it, too.
Yeah, yeah.
Akimoto, Asuka Construction Work in Progress.
Graduation commemorative edition will be on sale!
I'm Iyoki Mao.
This is Sugaura Sotsuki.
Please subscribe to our channel.
Bye bye!